[{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664030164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":14332,"timeElapsed":55045},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664040356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":10192,"timeElapsed":65237},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664045101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4743,"timeElapsed":69982},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664048077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2976,"timeElapsed":72958},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664051149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3071,"timeElapsed":76030},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664067551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":16401,"timeElapsed":92432},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664075192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":7640,"timeElapsed":100073},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664079488,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4295,"timeElapsed":104369},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664083369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3880,"timeElapsed":108250},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664094442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":9872,"timeElapsed":119323},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664100274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5832,"timeElapsed":125155},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664104090,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3815,"timeElapsed":128971},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664108091,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4000,"timeElapsed":132972},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664111427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3336,"timeElapsed":136308},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664114108,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2680,"timeElapsed":138989},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664119628,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5519,"timeElapsed":144509},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664122588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2959,"timeElapsed":147469},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664126029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3440,"timeElapsed":150910},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664129333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3304,"timeElapsed":154214},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664138454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":7728,"timeElapsed":163335},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664144455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6000,"timeElapsed":169335},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664148679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4224,"timeElapsed":173560},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664151271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2592,"timeElapsed":176152},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664154088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2816,"timeElapsed":178968},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664159888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5800,"timeElapsed":184769},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664162920,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3031,"timeElapsed":187801},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664173370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":10449,"timeElapsed":198250},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664175978,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2607,"timeElapsed":200858},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664199124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":22018,"timeElapsed":224005},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664203949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4824,"timeElapsed":228829},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664206917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2967,"timeElapsed":231798},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664210285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3368,"timeElapsed":235166},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664214149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3864,"timeElapsed":239030},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664219870,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":5720,"timeElapsed":244751},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664225686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":5816,"timeElapsed":250567},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664246809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":21122,"timeElapsed":271690},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664250449,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3639,"timeElapsed":275330},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664255737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":5288,"timeElapsed":280618},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664271691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":14721,"timeElapsed":296572},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664275035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3344,"timeElapsed":299916},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664278004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2967,"timeElapsed":302885},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664282532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4528,"timeElapsed":307413},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664285316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2784,"timeElapsed":310197},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664295133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":9816,"timeElapsed":320014},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664298181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":3048,"timeElapsed":323062},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664313751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":15569,"timeElapsed":338632},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664316855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3104,"timeElapsed":341736},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664328833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":10792,"timeElapsed":353713},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664331545,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2712,"timeElapsed":356426},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664334281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2736,"timeElapsed":359162},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664337153,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2872,"timeElapsed":362034},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664340034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2880,"timeElapsed":364915},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664345722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":5687,"timeElapsed":370603},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664350483,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":4760,"timeElapsed":375364},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664354667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4184,"timeElapsed":379548},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664358011,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":3343,"timeElapsed":382892},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664382358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":22921,"timeElapsed":407239},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664385566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":3208,"timeElapsed":410447},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664389647,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4080,"timeElapsed":414528},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664392087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2439,"timeElapsed":416968},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664395423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3336,"timeElapsed":420304},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664400968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":5544,"timeElapsed":425849},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664403640,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2671,"timeElapsed":428521},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664407608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3967,"timeElapsed":432489},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664410448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"164","question":"What is the last concert or performance you saw? Had you seen the band or performer before? Where?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2840,"timeElapsed":435329},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664419962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":8312,"timeElapsed":444843},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664425234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5272,"timeElapsed":450115},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664428162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2928,"timeElapsed":453043},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664430426,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2263,"timeElapsed":455307},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664433715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3288,"timeElapsed":458596},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664437531,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3816,"timeElapsed":462412},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664440195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2664,"timeElapsed":465076},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664484024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":43828,"timeElapsed":508905},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664487136,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"34","question":"What are you most afraid of?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3111,"timeElapsed":512017},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664503433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":15105,"timeElapsed":528314},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664506818,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3384,"timeElapsed":531699},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664512810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5992,"timeElapsed":537691},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664514931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2120,"timeElapsed":539812},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664518267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3335,"timeElapsed":543148},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664523019,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4752,"timeElapsed":547900},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664525932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2912,"timeElapsed":550813},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664537125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":11192,"timeElapsed":562006},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664539573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"55","question":"What do you think is the purpose of education?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":2448,"timeElapsed":564454},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664550094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":9416,"timeElapsed":574975},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664555391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5296,"timeElapsed":580272},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664561343,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5952,"timeElapsed":586224},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664564343,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2999,"timeElapsed":589224},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664566624,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2280,"timeElapsed":591505},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664569776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3151,"timeElapsed":594657},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664572344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2568,"timeElapsed":597225},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664575353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3007,"timeElapsed":600234},{"subjectID":"hhtl5w3uc7","prolificID":"600e5f4bec7cd96f1018caf9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215ce4d7d6b5350c7e16","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664578049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2696,"timeElapsed":602930}]